cinesouth.com 2005-04-03

# Privacy Policy for Cinesouth.com

#### We are committed to your privacy.

At Cinesouth, we believe strongly in protecting our users' privacy. You may choose to provide personal information at other times, such as when you enter a contest or ask that information be sent to you from one of our advertisers. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties except under the limited circumstances described below, and by using our service, you agree that we may do so. 

When you choose to send a greeting, you must provide your name, your email address and the name and email address of the recipient. This information is used to customize the mail and notify both you and the recipient that the greeting has been sent. Because we are committed to protecting your privacy, Cinesouth  will not disclose this information to third parties except under the limited circumstances described below. You may receive email communications from us regarding our products and services. Each of these messages will provide information on how to unsubscribe from future emails. 

In addition, we will not disclose your personal information to a third party unless we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Cinesouth; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our members or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false registration information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you -- including your computer's IP address -- may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions.)

Cinesouth does share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes. For example, we may tell our business partners how many customers in certain demographic groups sent certain mails. 

#### Mail Information

The information you provide to us is used to customize your greeting with the recipient's name and with your message, and to deliver an email notification to the recipient. We treat the mails as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of a mails, other than to the intended recipient, unless we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Cinesouth; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our members or the public. However, if you provide a false email address or attempt to pose as someone else when sending a mail, mail is subject to cancellation, and information about you -- including your computer's IP address -- be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions. Under normal circumstances, we will not monitor or edit the contents of the mails you send. On occasion, however, Cinesouth may need to view your message in connection with the technical processing of your greeting or the maintenance of our network. Also, if you ask one of our customer service representatives to help you send a card or to verify that a card was sent, that representative will be able to access all information about the card, including the recipient's email address and the message. 

#### Cookies

When you visit our site, Cinesouth may place a cookie on your computer's hard drive in order to improve our service to you. By automatically verifying that you are a member, the cookie makes it more convenient for you to use Cinesouth. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about which areas of our site are visited most frequently, this traffic information can be used to enhance the content of our site. 

If you've set your browser to reject cookies, you can still use our site, but you may need to re-enter information that we would normally obtain from the cookie. You can also set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies. If you do, you will receive a warning message each time our site attempts to place a cookie on your hard drive. 

Cookies also may be placed by our advertisers or by independent third parties that actually operate the servers on which the ads reside. Although Cinesouth encourages third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy standards and policies, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of such parties. 

#### Contests and Promotions

From time to time, Cinesouth may sponsor contests or promotions or allow other companies to sponsor contests or promotions on our site. In order to enter a contest or promotion, you may be asked to provide personal identifying information, and by doing so you agree that such information may be disclosed to the contest's sponsor, whose identity will be clearly indicated on the entry form. If Cinesouth is the sponsor of the contest or promotion, information you submit will be treated the same way we would treat your registration information. Other companies who sponsor or co-sponsor our contests and promotions may have their own policies for handling personal information, and information you submit will be subject to those policies as well. Although cinesouth encourages third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy standards and policies, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of such parties. 

#### Sponsors and Business Partners

Our sponsors also may offer you the opportunity to sign up for their services or information, such as fan clubs, newsletters or promotions. In these instances, we will inform you about exactly what personal information is requested by the sponsor (such as your email address), and we will ask you for permission to release your information to the sponsor. If you consent, Cinesouth will transfer your information to the sponsor. Once your information has been transferred to the sponsor, Cinesouth is not responsible for its use. The sponsor's use of the information is governed by the sponsor's privacy policy. While we encourage our third party sponsors to adhere to appropriate privacy standards, we are not responsible for the actions or policies of our sponsors. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.

  1. You can send email to [unsubscribe@cinesouth.com](mailto:unsubscribe@cinesouth.com)

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
